https://www.squirrelcart.com/index.php/privacy-policy

HomeFeaturesAll FeaturesDiscountsProduct Options & Add-OnsAccess RestrictionsEmailSales AgreementsAdd-On ModulesHandling & Order FeesSales Tax & VATAutomatic CategoriesHuman VerificationSecurity & SSLCart PersistenceImageSEO (search engine optimization)Code DetailsInventory ControlShippingCMS (Content Management System)Order ManagementSocial Sign-InCustomization & ThemesPaymentSpeed and PerformanceDatabaseProduct and CategoryStorefront ComponentsAll FeaturesAccess RestrictionsAdd-On ModulesAutomatic CategoriesCMS (Content Management System)Cart PersistenceCode DetailsCustomization & ThemesDatabaseDiscountsEmailHandling & Order FeesHuman VerificationImageInventory ControlOrder ManagementPaymentProduct Options & Add-OnsProduct and CategorySEO (search engine optimization)Sales AgreementsSales Tax & VATSecurity & SSLShippingSocial Sign-InSpeed and PerformanceStorefront ComponentsDemoPricingAll ProductsShopping Cart SoftwareAdd-On ModulesServices & SupportFAQAll FAQsRecurring Charges?Who Makes Squirrelcart?RequirementsRefund PolicyI Need a Web Host, Can You Help?Is Installation Easy?LicenseCustom FeaturesHow to InstallHow to CustomizeCan I Process Offline?How to UpgradeHow Do I Get Orders?Can I Change to Squirrelcart Pro?What to Order When UpgradingHow Long Has It Been Around?Real Stores Using SquirrelcartNewsDownloadContactSupportSupport HomeDocumentationForumsCheck Support StatusHelpdeskYour AccountLogin with UsAccount:Password: Remember me LoginForgot Password?Get an AccountLogin with FacebookLogin with GoogleLogin with TwitterPrivacy PolicyThank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.Collection of InformationWe collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.Cookie/Tracking TechnologyThe Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to	the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.Distribution of InformationWe may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation.	We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud	or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to	these companies for marketing purposes.Commitment to Data SecurityYour personally identifiable information is kept secure. All of your personal information is encrypted by SSL. SSL encrypts	your order information to avoid the decoding of that information by anyone other than Codelizard Web Services. Only authorized	employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information.	All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.Privacy Contact InformationIf you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us via email using our contact page.Future ChangesWe reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
